> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 还有一件事我想给你看
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: There's one more
thing that I wanna show you about
服务器端呈现。
server side rendering.
这是 SSR 分支中的第一个落实。
This is the first commit
in the SSR branch.
所以如果你进来了， >> Brian Holt: 我们的 repo 在这里，
So if you come into,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Our repo here,
SSR 有 SSR 分支
and there's an SSR branch, SSR.
>> Brian Holt: 您可以看到此处有两个用于 SSR的落实。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: You can see that there
are two commits in here for SSR.
其中一个将呈现为字符串
One of them uses render to string and
然后我要给你看第二个被称为节点串的
then I'm gonna show you a second
one called render to node string.
这是一个我非常兴奋的新 API 。
So this is a really new API
that I'm pretty excited about.
因此，请返回到 index.js， index.js 。
So go back to your index.js, index.js.
请转至 renderToString ，而我们将改为使用 renderToNodeStream 。
Go up to your renderToString and
we'll say renderToNodeStream instead.
> > 布莱恩・霍尔特:
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
there's kind of a new idea in
for， >> Brian Holt: 客户端框架
for,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Client-side frameworks
进行服务器端渲染，而不是只执行一个大的有效内容，
of doing server-side rendering, where
instead of doing just one big payload,
对，这就是我们现在正在做的事情。
right, that's what we're doing right now.
我们只是一次性把所有有效载荷都发送来对吧
We're just sending all
the payload all at once, right?
你只会在一次的时候开始渲染它对吧
That you just start rendering
pieces of it at a time, right?
所以你马上给他们发个片段
So that you immediately
send them a piece and
然后你再多给点些，所以你再多做一点。
then you wait to render a little bit more,
and so you render a little bit more.
然后你再多做一点，然后你就结束了，对吗 ?
And then you render a little bit more,
and then you finish, right?
所以这是一种进步的加载。
And so
it's kind of this progressive loading.
这太好了，因为现在我们可以马上给他们第一部分，
This is great because now we can
immediately send them the first part that
我们已经有了，对吧 ?
we already have, right?
当我们完成服务器端时，他们可以开始加载所有 CSS
And they can start loading all the CSS
while we're finishing server side
渲染，是吧 ?
rendering, right?
我们的应用不是很大的，所以这不会带来巨大的差异。
Our app is not very big, so this is not
gonna make that big of a difference.
但如果你有一个 LinkedIn 大小的应用程序
But if you have a LinkedIn sized
application that's gonna be a massive
为你赢得胜利
win for you.
你可以像这样刮 100 到 400 毫秒。
You can literally shave 100 to 400
milliseconds off just like that.
所以我们要修改一下这个
So we're gonna modify
this a little bit here.
所以我们要做的第一件事就是我们要说
So the very, very first thing that
we're gonna do here is we're gonna say
res.write (部件[0])。
res.write(parts[0]).
所以我们马上就能清空用户了
So we're immediately
gonna flush the users.
这里有这些 CSS 和下载
Here is all these CSS and
go download this,
我要赶着背景来呈现我的 JavaScript 对吧
and I'm gonna hurry in the background
render my JavaScript, right?
所以我们先做这个
So we do this first.
然后我们要做个小溪
Then we're gonna make a stream,
它表示 const stream =renderToNodeStream(reattMarkup)。
it says const stream
=renderToNodeStream(reactMarkup).
这会逐渐地呈现你的应用程序，对吧 ?
And this is gonna progressively
render your app, right?
一次一片片就会冲掉那些
One piece at a time,
it's just gonna flush pieces of those out
称为节点流，它是一种特定类型的节点数据结构，
to what's called a node stream, which is a
specific kind of node data structure that
随着时间的推移逐渐地向您提供数据，对吧 ?
progressively gives you data over time,
right?
然后我就会说
And then here I'm gonna say
stream.pipe(res end: false))。
stream.pipe(res end: false)).
>> Brian Holt: 接下来，你会说 " 结束"。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then here
you're gonna say stream.on('end'.
>> Brian Holt: 会说 res.write(parts[1]) 和
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: It's gonna
say res.write(parts[1]) and
重新点好吗
res.end, okay?
然后我们就可以把这些东西都掉在这儿了
And then we can just drop all
this stuff here at the end, oops.
35 和 34 你可以删除
35 and 34 you can just delete.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，此 res.pipe 或 stream.pipe 表示
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So this res.pipe here or
the stream.pipe saying like
把这些东西都管起来把管子连接到这管子上
pipe all this stuff into,
connect this pipe to this pipe.
将所有标记发送到 res，响应用户，但是
Send all the markup into the res,
the response to the user, but
一旦完成了就别结束了
don't end it once it's done.
这就是那部分的意思
That's what that part means.
然后这里说一旦你写完其他的 HTML
Then here it says, once you're finished
write the other bit of the HTML and
然后断开连接。
then cut the connection.
我们完蛋了对吧
We're finished, right?
再一次
Now again,
我们不会注意到我们在 localhost 上的任何区别吧
we're not gonna notice any difference
cuz we're on the localhost, right?
因此，如果我执行 npm 运行，请 >> Brian Holt: 此
So if I do npm run start,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: This
还会以同样的方式工作
is still gonna work
relatively the same way.
>> Brian Holt: 可能。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Possibly.
>> Brian Holt: 那么我要回什么 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So what am I getting back?
> > Brian Holt: 好吧，这行吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Well,
this works okay, right?
> > Brian Holt: 嗯，好的，看起来很好。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Yeah, okay,
seems like it's working okay.
>> Brian Holt: 在这里有第二个承诺，在这个特殊的存储库中。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So there's a second
commit here, in this particular repo.
他们也会有 renderToNodeStream 工作。
They'll have the renderToNodeStream
working as well.
>> Brian Holt: 有任何问题吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Any questions about that?
>> Brian Holt: 因此，如果您有能力执行流，那么这是首选项。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So this is preferable if
you have the ability to do streams and
处理诸如  或长时间运行的 HTML 请求或 HTTP 请求。
handle things like HTTP2 or long
running HTML requests or HTTP requests.
这是最好的做法。
This is preferable.
这对你来说快一点了
This will be faster for
you, almost always.
我无法想象当世界不会是什么时候，但最着名的最后一个词。
I can't imagine when the in world
wouldn't be, but famous last words.
但是，这是服务器端呈现。
But yeah, that's server-side rendering.
所以我要重置我的回购协议了
So I'm gonna reset my repo now.
我要说它重置了 HEAD ( 硬 )
I'm going to say git reset HEAD --hard,
然后把它洗干净
and then git clean -f.
> > Brian Holt: 那是很多东西，好，很酷。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: That was a lot of stuff,
all right, cool.